alice.com 2012-05-11

# Alice.com

This Privacy Policy forms part of the Alice.com Account Agreement and is incorporated by reference therein. Your privacy is very important to us. This Policy describes the information we collect about you and how we use this information. By using the Alice.com service and website, you agree that you have read and understand this Privacy Policy and you consent to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Information Alice Collects

Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a positive experience while you use Alice.com, to allow you to set up an Account to shop and make product purchases from Alice.com and the manufacturer storefronts that we operate, and to provide you with access to product offers, promotions, coupons and free product samples through the Alice service. Alice may collect both personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") and information about your use of Alice.com services and website that is not connected to your Personal Information ("Non-personal Information"). 

### Non-personal Information

Non-personal Information may include both: 1) technical information, such as the type of Internet browser you use, the date and time you access the website, and your Internet protocol address; and, 2) service usage information, such as your site visits and page views, search and purchase history, and the demographic, geographic and psychographic information, product reviews and other feedback you supply to Alice. Alice may share Non-personal Information with select third parties on an anonymous basis (i.e., in a way that does not connect your Non-personal Information to your Personal Information or disclose your Personal Information in any fashion). 

### Personal Information

Personal Information may include your name, street address, email address, telephone number and payment information.

### Alice Disclosure of Your Personal Information.

Except as explicitly set forth herein, we will not disclose your Personal Information to third parties without your express permission.

### Agents

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include providing customer service tools, fulfilling orders, delivering packages, hosting our website, analyzing data, or processing credit card payments. Our agents may have access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

### Compelled Disclosures 

We may disclose your Personal Information as required by law and as necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, and/or legal process served on us; and/or to protect our rights and the rights of our customers.

### Business Transfers

In the event that Alice.com, Inc., or substantially all of our assets are sold, customer information, including Personal Information, will likely be one of the transferred assets.

### Manufacturer Storefronts

We power a number of manufacturer branded storefronts that allow consumers to access and purchase products directly from a manufacturer’s own web site (e.g., laundrysoap.com) without visiting the main Alice.com website. If you first accessed and created your Alice.com account from one of these branded manufacturer stores, both Alice.com and the individual manufacturer that controls the store will have access to your Personal Information. If you signed up for Alice from the main Alice.com website, this subparagraph does not apply to you. 

### Alice.com Account and Communications

In order to place an order on the Alice.com website or from a branded manufacturer storefront, you need to set up an Account, which may include your name, e-mail address, password, mailing address and payment information. You can review, update and change some of your Personal Information―including your email address, mailing address and password―in your Account at anytime. In addition to using your email to contact you regarding Account activities, we may also update you on new product offerings and communications relevant to your use of Alice.com (Alice updates). If you do not wish to receive Alice updates, you have the ability to stop receiving these email communications by signing into your Account and changing your communication preferences at anytime. You can remove yourself from Alice updates by clicking on an “unsubscribe” hyperlink contained in any update e-mail that we send to you.

### Customer Supplied Information

The Alice.com website has a number of social features that allow you to interact with other Alice customers and to post and share information about yourself, your use of the Alice service, and the products you buy (Customer Supplied Information). This Customer Supplied Information may contain Personal Information you submit, such as your name. By submitting such content on our website and/or utilizing our social features, you consent to our sharing of that information with others. You will always have the option to not include your Personal Information through the Alice website social features (for example, by not submitting your name in association with a product review, or requesting that your customer profile on Alice or portions of that profile be kept confidential). 

### Security of Information

Alice uses security measures to protect the privacy of your Personal Information. We limit the employees and contractors that can access your Personal Information and require these employees and contractors to adhere to a confidentiality policy. Alice also uses technological security measures to protect your Personal Information. However, transmissions over the Internet are not completely secure, and any information you send to or through Alice.com may be accessible by others. Alice cannot guarantee our security measures. We also strongly encourage you to keep your password and account information secure and confidential. 

### Cookies 

Cookies are small files that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable us to recognize you when you return to our website. Cookies let us identify you to provide you a personalized experience on our website. We use cookie and web beacon technology to track which pages on our sites our visitors view. Cookies and web beacons do not contain any Personal Information. Most Internet browsers permit you to erase or block cookies. Please note that if you configure your browser to remove or reject cookies, you will not be able to use the full functionality of our website. 

### Children

Children are not eligible for an Alice.com Account and we ask that minors (under the age of eighteen (18)) do not submit any personal information to us. By using Alice.com services you represent to Alice that you are at least 18 years old.

### Notification of Changes

Alice may make periodic changes to this privacy policy and changes will be posted on the Alice.com web site. We may also notify you by e-mail if there is a material change in our privacy practices or policies. Your continued use of your Account or the Alice.com web site shall constitute your acceptance of any such amendment.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site or your dealings with Alice.com, please contact us ([support@alice.com](mailto:support@alice.com)) 

REVISED 12/08/09
